https://rmhctulsa.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Ronald McDonald House - Tulsa
[Skip to Content]
Menu
Search for:
PRIVACY POLICY
Ronald McDonald House Charities of Tulsa, Inc. (RMHT) is pleased to provide information about its privacy policy. Please be assured that RMHT uses its best efforts regarding privacy protection and data security.
Types of Information Collected and How It Is Used
RMHT gathers personal information, such as first and last names, home addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and credit card numbers, only when voluntarily submitted by you. If you make a donation, personal information will be collected from you in order to process that donation.
With your permission, we will use personal information collected from you to send you information, such as RMHT updates or information regarding new Ronald McDonald House openings, fundraising campaigns or major grant initiatives. If you do not elect to receive such materials, we will not send them to you.
Security of Donor Information
Donor information is stored within a donor management database within RMHT. Access to the database is restricted to personnel with a legitimate business need to access or modify the information contained therein.
Sharing of Personal Information
Companies may be engaged by RMHT to perform a variety of functions, such as assisting with donation collection, providing technical services for our Internet sites, etc. Such companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform certain functions. However, these companies may use such personal information only for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose.
Other than as provided in this privacy policy, RMHT does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties.
RMHT reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a public safety matter.
Access
You are in control of all personal information you provide to us. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us, you can let us know by contacting us at the following addresses: Ronald McDonald House Charities, Inc., Attn: Privacy Department, 6102 S Hudson Ave. or email: info@rmhctulsa.org. In order to review any personal information, we have about you or to ask us to delete that information or to stop further use of the information, please contact us through the email or postal address listed above. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email list, please use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our newsletter emails or contact us through the postal address listed above. It may take up to two weeks to remove you from all of our correspondences, if we have one in production when you request to be removed.
Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for recordkeeping purposes. Cookies allow a certain Internet site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most Internet sites, RMHT uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your online experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site on an anonymous, aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the site. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in that instance.
Use the options in your Internet browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the “Help” section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of the RMHT website.
We use Google services, such as Google Analytics, as well as other third party vendors that place first-party and/or third-party cookies on a browser across our websites. To opt out of Google tracking, please visit their opt-out page. We also use Google AdWords “remarketing” to market our sites across the web. We place a cookie on a browser, and then Google reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. You may opt out of this ad serving on Google’s opt out page. If you are concerned about 3rd party cookies served by networks, you should also visit the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Links to Other Sites
We may offer links to sites that are not operated by RMHT. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies.
Payment Processing and Data Storage
Ronald McDonald House Tulsa Charities uses Elavon Inc. products for payment processing and data storage. Elavon has modified every one of its applications that processes, stores and transmits cardholder data based on PCI DSS and PA-DSS compliance standards. Elavon fully adheres to PCI standards regarding secure storage of data, strong access control and other requirements. For further information on this subject please visit Elavon’s PCI Compliance Resources.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy became effective on April 15, 2016. From time to time, it may be necessary for RMHT to change its privacy policy, so we suggest that you check here periodically. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.
NEWSLETTER SIGNUP
Sign up for our e-newsletter to read inspiring stories from our families, keep up to date with RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. news and stay in touch with your fellow RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. friends and supporters.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
Sign Up
Jobs
Online Giving
Form 990
© RMHC
The following trademarks used herein are owned by McDonald's Corporation and its affiliates; McDonald's, Ronald McDonald House Charities, Ronald McDonald House Charities Logo, RMHC of Tulsa, Inc., Ronald McDonald House, Ronald McDonald Family Room, and Ronald McDonald Care Mobile.
RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. is recognized as a public charity under Internal Revenue Code section 509(a) and has 501(c)(3) status. Donations to RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. are deductible. Donors should consult their tax advisor for questions regarding deductibility. The RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. EIN is 73-1313892. A copy of the RMHC of Tulsa, Inc. determination letter is available upon request.
©2020
RMH Tulsas, LLC. All Rights Reserved. Website hosting & design by Skynet Solutions
X
THANK YOU
FOR HELPING FAMILIES FIND STRENGTH IN NUMBERS.
You’ve just joined your fellow RMHC ambassadors in pledging your support by signing up for our e-newsletter. With your help, more families will find strength in one another so their children can be strong enough to heal. Our e-newsletter delivers relevant content that will educate you, inspire you and show you that RMHC and our families wouldn’t be as strong without you.
Your friends at Ronald McDonald House Tulsa
